extasycams.com 2009-04-18

# Live Adult Cams, cheap live girls chat webcam and cam2cam.

**PRIVACY POLICY**   
How ExtasyCams Protects Your Privacy

Summary: 

  * We **NEVER** sell, rent or share your personal information or email address with any other party. 
  * We may send you occasional promotional emails, and every email will contain an unsubscribe option. 
  * Your personal information is **never** stored on ExtasyCams.com's server, so it cannot be stolen by hackers. 

Below are the complete details of our privacy policy: 

Not only do we respect your privacy, we protect your privacy. 

ExtasyCams is occasionally contacted by third parties who, for marketing purposes, want to purchase our mailing list and other sensitive customer information derived from our database. Although there is no law forbidding ExtasyCams from selling such information, the trading of which is an extremely lucrative business , ExtasyCams is serious in its commitment to protecting your personal privacy. We have never sold such personal information about our customers to outside parties -- not even once -- and we don't intend to. 

As a general rule, ExtasyCams doesn't collects any kind of information about you.

Log information bears greater explanation: Log information typically consists of such things as your browser type (i.e., Netscape or MSIE), your IP address (i.e., 102.316.52.11), the domain name from which you are visiting ExtasyCams (i.e., "aol.com"), and which pages of ExtasyCams that you visit. Like all internet services, we analyze our log files to better understand which areas of ExtasyCams are more popular than others. And like most other large-scale internet properties, we also use this information to "customize" the ExtasyCams experience to match your tastes. For example, if you first visit ExtasyCams by searching an internet portal for a search term such as "voyeur" and clicking upon an ExtasyCams banner or link, ExtasyCams may set a "cookie" on your computer which records the term as a "search preference" (Note: Everyday log-analysis programs such as WebTrends include such tracking of keyword-specific traffic as a regular feature - indeed, using such tools, the administrators of most websites on earth track traffic originating from search engines by searched keyword). Later, as you navigate through ExtasyCams, you will likely observe that the content you see on ExtasyCams tends to be tailored to match your recorded search preference. Note: such cookies are "secure" in that they cannot be read by other internet companies, but can only be read by the web site which placed the cookie. 

ExtasyCams also uses your recorded "search preference" information to better target and allocate marketing expenditures. For example, if ExtasyCams learns that, in aggregate, individuals who search portals for terms such as "voyeur" are more likely to purchase goods and services from ExtasyCams than individuals who search for terms such as "livecams", ExtasyCams may allocate greater portions of its marketing budget to targeting the former group, and a smaller portion of its budget to target the latter group. By optimizing marketing strategies in this manner, ExtasyCams has more disposable capital that can be deployed toward development efforts which improve the ExtasyCams platform and provide a richer customer experience for all. 

Speaking of cookies, another kind of cookie that ExtasyCams sets is an "identification cookie". This cookie is written whenever you successfully use your login and password to access a restricted area of ExtasyCams; the identification cookie is available only to individuals who have already been verified as adults, via ExtasyCams' verification procedures. When ExtasyCams' servers observe this identification cookie on your computer, they recognize you and therefore might deliver unmodified content as opposed to modified content - in effect, another form of customized content tailored to suit your indicated preferences. 

Another question that should concern you: "Does ExtasyCams outsource to other companies any privacy-sensitive functions such as management of its email newsletter system, web hosting, or its e-commerce platform?" Because ExtasyCams is committed to safeguarding the integrity of your personal information, we have elected to not use such services, despite the fact that they are reasonably-priced and simplify the management task of running a large and complex website operation.
